<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://harlandzzc.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://harlandzzc.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-09-25T07:10:51+00:00</updated><id>https://harlandzzc.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Haolin&apos;s Personal Webpage. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">17 Suggestions from My Supervisor</title><link href="https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/suggestions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="17 Suggestions from My Supervisor"/><published>2024-10-12T04:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-10-12T04:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/suggestions</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/suggestions/"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Avoid seeking quick success.</li> <li>Be like a sponge, learn from books, materials, and others.</li> <li>Stay humble, modest, and listen more. Everyone has strengths. Learn from both the older and younger generations.</li> <li>Be pragmatic. Do more, talk less. Practice and apply your knowledge.</li> <li>Be truthful and grounded. Stay hands-on and ensure you’re constantly learning. During the learning phase, focus more on input than output.</li> <li>Build a solid foundation in mathematics and physics and maintain a broad academic vision.</li> <li>Develop strong programming skills; run tutorial codes frequently.</li> <li>Dedicate 4 hours daily to studying math, physics, and research papers, and another 4 hours to coding. Execution is key.</li> <li>Once you reach a certain level, you’ll engage in more meaningful academic exchanges. Strengthen your core competencies.</li> <li>The quality of research is more important than the quantity. Each paper should be of high quality with clean, open-source code that benefits others.</li> <li>Nurturing scientific literacy and potential is more crucial than publishing many papers.</li> <li>Approach your work with the humility of a first-year graduate student. Go through the same learning path as a master’s student.</li> <li>Everyone’s PhD journey is unique; focus on uncovering your own distinctiveness.</li> <li>Contribute valuable work to the academic community.</li> <li>The ranking of your school or lab’s achievements is not directly related to your personal success. Focus on your own results.</li> <li>Be altruistic.</li> <li>Strive to be a thoughtful and deep-thinking PhD student.</li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="PhD"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're just starting your PhD journey, these suggestions could be helpful.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra</title><link href="https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra"/><published>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://harlandzzc.github.io/blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing updates across our Gemini family of models and a glimpse of Project Astra, our vision for the future of AI assistants.]]></summary></entry></feed>